paymo.net 2011-12-30

# BOKU Privacy Policy | BOKU

Boku, Inc. (for itself, and on behalf of its subsidiaries and affiliated entities, “Boku”) is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. We value your trust and want you to understand how we protect, collect, use and disclose the personal information you share with us.

This privacy statement applies to personal information we obtain anytime you interact with Boku such as when you visit our website (boku.com), use the Boku mobile payment service (“Boku Service”) with a participating Merchant (“Merchant”) or contact Boku support. We want to ensure you are aware of our practices for collecting and processing personal information, which is information about a person that can be used to identify that person. This privacy statement does not apply to Merchants accessing and using the Merchant portions of our website. The collection, use and disclosure of Merchant data and information is governed by the legal agreement between Boku and Merchant.

What we collect  
We collect personal information to process transactions when using the Boku Service, provide services, and administer our business. The type of personal information we collect when using the Boku Service may include contact information such as mobile number, wireless network, country, billing amount and Merchant or such other information we may collect with your consent or as permitted or required by law.

How we use it  
We use personal information in a number of ways such as to complete your transaction, administer any problems that may arise in effecting the transaction, to better understand and manage our ongoing relationship with you, to assure good service, to prevent fraud and abuse, for purposes of verification and risk management and otherwise with consent or as permitted or required by law. Boku may store personal information on databases for the purposes of the administration of our business, including our ongoing relationship with you, for market research and, only with your consent, for direct marketing purposes. As permitted by applicable law, we may merge personal information with public information or other information received from reputable vendors to update contact information or to enhance demographic profiles. We will retain your information for a minimum of 5 years or as necessary to comply with our legal obligations or resolve disputes. If you wish to request that we remove your information from our systems and no longer provide you with services you may contact us.

Who we share it with  
Boku will not sell, rent, or lease your personal information. We may share all of the information, as described above, with Merchants, our affiliates and our agents in connection with goods and services these parties perform for, or with, Boku for the uses described in “How we use it” and for other purposes as permitted or required by law. In particular, use of your personal information for marketing purposes by Boku and/or our agents will always be made with your consent and in compliance with the applicable law regarding customer consent. Disclosures permitted or required by law may include cooperation with criminal or government investigations, fraud prevention and detection, and responses to a court order or subpoena. Boku agents are bound by appropriate data safeguarding obligations. Our Merchants, agents and affiliates may be located outside the European Economic Area.

Boku may disclose some or all of the personal information to Merchants and service providers for the purposes of processing requested transactions, improving the user experience or to perform business support functions on our behalf. Our agreements with service providers will contain confidentiality provisions and restrictions on using this information for any other purpose. If Boku becomes involved in a merger, acquisition or any form of sale of some or all its assets, we may disclose personal information to third parties in connection with the evaluation of the transaction. The surviving company, or the acquiring company in the case of a sale of assets, would have access to personal information that would continue to be subject to this privacy statement.

Choice  
Boku will not use or share your personal information in ways incompatible with the ones described above without providing you a choice. You must opt-out of any sharing of personal information you have authorized or consented to as described above. However, to the extent that applicable law requires express consent or “opt-in” for the collection and use of personal information, Boku will maintain processes and procedures to ensure such information is collected with express consent. Your mobile number will not be used to directly market Boku services unless that possible use has been disclosed and a choice provided.

Accuracy & Access  
Boku is committed to ensuring that the information we obtain and use about you is accurate for its intended purpose. You can contact us at any time to review, update, delete or correct (for future use) your personally identifiable information maintained by Boku. We will reply to your request within thirty (30) days of submission. You can help us maintain accurate records by informing us of changes or modifications to your personal information.

Data Security  
Boku utilizes physical, electronic and procedural security measures to protect against loss, misuse, and alteration of information under our control. Boku offers industry–standard practices and security measures to safeguard and secure the personal information we collect.

Access to personal information is restricted to Merchants, employees and service providers who need to have access to that information as described in this privacy statement. Boku requires its service providers to observe standards with respect to the security, collection, use and sharing of personal information, and to comply with applicable law. We make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems. Despite our efforts, we cannot guarantee that personal information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of our administrative, managerial and technical safeguards. When you enter sensitive information such as your mobile number, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

If Boku learns of a security systems breach we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using the Boku Service, you agree that Boku may communicate with you electronically or via short messaging service (SMS). Boku may post a notice on the Boku website if a security breach occurs. Boku may also send you an email to you at the email address, if any, you have provided to us or send you an SMS to the mobile number you have provided to us. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice of a security breach) you should notify us.

Preventing Identity Theft  
Boku is dedicated to protecting your personal information. We will never initiate a request for personal information from you by fax or email. Please do not send confidential personal information such as social security numbers, government identification numbers, or account numbers to Boku via an unsecured email message. You may send confidential information to Boku via posted mail, phone or contact us. Do not be misled by emails that appear to be from us and ask for personal information. If you receive a suspicious email requesting your personal information, please forward the email immediately to fraud@boku.com. To report fraud to the Internet Fraud Complaint Center, visit www.ic3.gov. This is a partnership between The FBI and the National White Collar Crime Center.

Browsing  
When you browse our websites or request pages, we automatically collect certain technical information about your visit. Examples of this standard type of information include the type of Internet browser you use, your IP address, browser headers, the files you request and the domain name and country from which you request information. We use this type of technical information to make our website function correctly, to better understand how visitors use our website and to improve the website, its contents and functionality to meet your needs. As part of our efforts to protect customers from fraud, this information is also used to assist in authenticating who you are when you access the website.

Cookies  
Some of our web pages may contain “cookies”, or data that is sent to your web browser and stored on your computer. The purpose of these “cookies” is to allow our server to recognize you as a Boku customer if you return to the website using the same computer and browser. In the event you do not wish to receive such cookies, you usually may configure your web browser to not accept cookies or to notify you if a cookie is sent to you. You are free to decline cookies if your web browser permits, but you may not be able to use all the features and the functionality of our websites. Boku does not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our website.

Privacy practices of third parties  
Boku is not responsible for the content or information practices employed by other websites that are linked to or from our website or which use the Boku Service. In most cases where links are provided, they are provided as pointers to information on services that may be useful to users. These sites and the Merchant sites providing mobile payment services using the Boku Service are governed by their own privacy statements. You are encouraged to review the privacy statement of these other websites before providing them with personal information.

Third Party Cookies  
The use of cookies by our partners, Merchants and service providers is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, Merchants and service providers may use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

Use by Children  
Boku will not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13, without the consent of a parent or guardian.

Change in Privacy Statement  
At Boku, your trust is one of our most important assets. We will continually work to protect the privacy of our customers and will continually review our privacy policy. This website will always contain the most current privacy statement. If we decide to change our privacy practices, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we change how we use your personally identifiable information, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

TRUSTe  
Boku has been awarded TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe’s program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/index.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. TRUSTe’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us. If you are not satisfied with our response you can [contact TRUSTe](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).

For more information or if you have questions  
Should you have further questions regarding our privacy statement or about how your personal information is used, you can contact us.

BOKU, Inc.  
201 Mission Street, 10th Floor  
San Francisco, California 94105  
USA
